Unknown: Hi everyone is Shiva Jonghwan ko ek and yo Sajha Eureka ito the collocation Jonghwan? Hello everybody, welcome everyone to this special talk by Professor Peter skilling. It's a great honor that we could have Professor shear to talk to all our translators and people who are interested in this research and translation of Tibetan canon. Professor is a very, very gentle kind scholar and translator and we look forward to this light chat, but at the same time, a very knowledgeable journey with professor. And it's also a great honor that we have Professor Lee Shanghai here, who is going to be the main person who lead this discussion session on behalf of the Kumar Jeeva project. We hope that after this talk, we will still have many opportunities to learn from Professor Peter skilling. Thank you for coming today and let's start the talk neelesh no juggling how
cautious is okay. Thank you, Jennifer. So, let me start with an introduction and then we will give it to professor's stealing and then you are starting to talk. So, Professor Peter skilling was a professor at the CO francais. Dixon more diction, oriented, exist life French, none almost non existent French pronunciation. So the school which is based in Bangkok. He was a professor till his retirement in 2017. And currently he still holds several academic positions. He is the visiting kintu foundation professor of Buddhist studies, as well as adjunct professor at Savithri by Pouliot, buena University being appointed in the department of the Pali and Buddhist studies, and he's also a special lecturer at Chulalongkorn University in Bangkok, an Honorary Associate at the Department of Indian subcontinental Studies University of Sydney. She has been a visiting professor at a number of leading academic institutions around the world, including Harvard University and University of California at Berkeley, University of Oxford, Sydney University, Soca University, and Savithri by Palais buena University. Professor skilling is one of the world's pre eminent scholars in the Buddhist cultures of South Asia, Southeast Asia and Tibet, having worked in such diverse disciplines as history, archaeology, ethnography, art, and also philosophy. He has published and edited many books. I think, with this new one that we're talking about and counting already 10 books, maybe they're more and he's He has published articles for more than 45 years. In some years, you would publish as many as 10 articles in one single calendar year, so you can count how many articles there must have been. Apart from being a scholar of Buddhist texts. Professor skilling is also the founder of the fragile palm leaves Foundation, an initiative to preserve Buddhist literature of Southeast Asia. We've gathered together in this digital space to hear him speak about his new publication, questioning the Buddha, a selection of 25 sutras from wisdom publications. Today's event is organized by the Kumara Jiva project and initiative to translate texts in the Congo and Dangar that is the Tibetan Buddhist canon into Chinese language. So in addition to hearing about this work from the author and translator himself, this event also provides an occasion for aspiring translators to interact with Professor skilling, who has offered in this volume 25 Tibetan sutras in exemplary English translation. Professor skilling has made very significant contributions to the study of Tibetan Buddhist canon in a subfield that is known as congenial studies field which was operating most actively, maybe about 25 years ago. He's also written major studies on the history and formation of the Tibetan Buddhist canon. In the present work, Professor skilling has written a long introduction of what I would call the history of Buddhist texts, or history of Buddhist scriptures. This new account is most up to date reflecting the current state of our knowledge of Buddhist scriptures. The introduction covers the early periods of Buddhist texts, where he also draws from his vast knowledge of Indian Buddhism and also Pali studies. So without further ado, let me turn this to Professor Peter skilling.
Thank you very much, very good to see you and others here in Taipei after some time. Thank you very much for the invitation to the commodity project. And so we will discuss this book question the Buddha. I have a few references. They're actually mostly in a unfinished printed paper which is a parallel to this. Anyway, that's qB. There happened to be references. And I am now finishing I have finished actually have submitted Buddha's words for tough times anthology. This will be 20 translations from Tibetan, Sanskrit and Pali. This will be forthcoming I open 2023. This is a mixed translations from several languages. I prefer to not be I think we have to think outside the box. If we're studying Tibetan fine, but we should look outside the box if we study probably fine. And when we can we can let some Tibetans or Chinese scholars into the box or transcend the walls. Because this I think what we really need, I'm not think I haven't got the right word for it. It's cross fertilization is one word, but that is a bit agricultural. It may be intertextual, where we should let the different cannons I start with the principle that there are four Canons for great canons of wisdom. And there is the Tibetan and associated with that is the Mongolian there is the Chinese canon, or there are the Chinese canons. And there is the Pali canon. And we should encourage the interaction of these experience. So I would like to today is celebration for me, my father's I think 120th birthday is coming up. So I dedicate this talk to my father, he's just giving Mexicans and to my mother. So we write this, so I how do we learn? I guess we learned very young I've learned probably an awful lot from my father who was a scholar of Central Europe. And so I think I absorbed aspects of attitude and methodology from my father, so I am grateful for that. Please
now, where did I start? That's a long story. But I say where did I start with Tibetan studies in Tibetan language that was in what Benjamin bofit The marble temple in Bangkok in about 1970 And I was a monk at that time there were several Tibetan monks resident there and they very kindly gave me experts gave me resins in reading Tibetan I have Yeah. Good chance. I don't have pictures of all of them. Llama yesterday in fact, I met in India but he came to to Thailand. And these happy smiles are the people who've taught me Tibetan I'm sorry the first one very embarrassed I forget his name. Second one guess it up something gig died very recently after a long stay in southern France where he was a teacher Fletcher yoga knee and wow, first one is mama so sorry. Tenzin that taught me very much. There are several others can go into the detail take too much time whose pictures I could not get. Next please. So that is where it began in this beautiful temple called the marble temple, one of the tourist spots of Bangkok. The abbot there, my preceptor permitted me to borrow Kanjur volumes of the alternately what I call alternately reprint, a clicking can Jura Beijing capture published in alternate Japan and so I could borrow the volumes and read through them with these two rather than scholars their next please has very famous, beautiful Next please. And they also benefited a bit late and about the same time bit writer from venerable some dead pranayama somewhere to what time Terra. He, at that time, he was the abbot of what Pavani wait. And then he went on to become the Sangha Raja of Thailand and lived to the ripe age of 100 years. He also basically permitted me to borrow volumes of the Kanjur from his library, his temple library. And that was a great help for my studies. Next please. Some people I only some masters, I have the blessing of seeing very briefly, but to see and meet someone like color MPJ even for an evening talk, or a few times later, even for just a glance, is great. Inspiration stays with one. So it's a great thing to meet teachers. Next please. Another was Melinda G. Anagarika. Indra next place in Bodhgaya. He was an energy was never actually my direct teacher. But he taught me so much through his example, walking through the fields around put Gaia and so on his insight and humor. SN Goenka also passed away. And I had the teacher in Bangkok of key suepo or so I'm grateful to all of this for their dharma teaching and for their especially for their example, example of people who are full of joy, compassion and good humor. It's very helpful experts and I guess finally in this list, which is very incomplete list is my heart goes on under Cambodia,
who at that time was sort of stuck in Thailand because of the war in Cambodia. So I had the benefit of learning. Are we from him asking him questions and also I do not have a picture from bedroom Bonaga Cena an Indian, the cook was also in Thailand, often with Buddha dasa. He was the first translator with a dasa because next please and venerable some Dong Ling put j in Sarnath. Next please. How did I learn about the Kanjur and tenger? These are some of the things I think I said I will talk about so I will mention them briefly. As please. In terms of access, I use the attorney catalog next place produced in attorney University in Kyoto, and I got the lucky habit of reading catalogs. Then you learn from these catalogs, what is in
Kendra, here
are also there's a tenger catalog. Now you reading the catalogue, you see it in the Tibetan language, the Sanskrit language with comparative notes about the Chinese translations in Chinese Tripitaka. Unfortunately, I don't benefit much from that, but I know what's there. So this was a great pioneering work of the 1930s in cancer studies. A pioneering Western work that I've added to the front is by Ray unfair. And the analysis of Kanjur which is actually a translation into French from the English of Samantha Kurose Alexandria, someone that Kurose done in the 1820s. So these, I don't have pictures of that, but some of the Kurose was a great pioneer for European study of Tibetan classical literature. Next please. Fair also made an edition of vedana shutter count 100 as Adonis explains so he made a translation of some of the curses. Now most of the conjecture based on the narc tongue I'm not sure he added much to that next place. So, the other important work of fair is the extracts from the kanji this big book is is and was and maybe is the largest collection of kanji or texts in European language and I think remains so, today in French, so, very beneficial to those who are new French. Now, of course, all translations carry old information in some ways or mistakes and so on, but they are extremely valuable whenever I start to study a new text I go first shoulder Kurose see what he said about it often his short two or three lines summary is right on sometimes it might be a bit off the Sanskrit might be off, but these are pioneering works then I go to this then I go through the new catalogs to see its history Next please. So, ah sometime when input J was a word, a member of the Committee of the Krishna Murthy center on the banks of the Ganga near Sarnoff and Krishna Marty was a rather extraordinary individual who was also happy, fortunate to have met and listen to
next place so, when we translate, we need space. So, we have to think of the sky and our thoughts are like passing clouds. I suppose we have to try to catch them sometimes, otherwise, let them go. So we have to be open, like the sky to all the different perspectives, concepts, challenges that we meet when we translate. Next please. I didn't have time to sketch this out in any kind of plan, I tried to method follows what I could call the palimpsests principle. That means to say that the palimpsest means a piece of ancient writing not necessarily ancient, a piece of writing, which is written over an earlier text, which has not been erased or has been not fully erased, so that we can see the earlier text through the later writing. This mainly used for ancient manuscripts in European studies, but I use it in a slightly different sense, in that behind the Tibetan translation, not exactly erased, we can try to see the Indic texts, the Sanskrit texts. Now, this is a problem for translators both into English or into Chinese or into any language, because if they don't know, Sanskrit, then they say what can I do? And I shouldn't I should say go and learn Sanskrit but not everyone can do that. Or it takes time as well. So the This principle is going to be done word by word, that is to say to try to learn to build up the vocabulary behind the translations to understand the Sanskrit vocabulary. Now I strange habits that reading dictionaries and catalogs, I started with, I have my kind of principle is that I try to know Tibetan and Sanskrit and English the three languages in question, as best I can, just very imperfectly. Tibetan means classical Tibetan language of the Tanger texts, because they translate sutras that means the language of the first mainly the first diffusion of the Dharma. This is the age of the Mojave potty chatter to talk about a PR tempo, and the Medea with petty torture bumper, Nuba I call that the companion to the Mojave potty. So, these two works are available in additions, we need a more better relation of them, but they are there. So, these are wonderful works of lexicography. That I think we have to have by our side, like give the key to the Sanskrit terms behind the Tibetan translations, these are the official translation, translation is proclaimed or ordained by the Dharma kings. Now, there are can be other possibilities and so on, and some words are not there. And then we use dictionaries, indexes all kinds of materials, so builds up to quite a lot. For the Sanskrit of the palimpsest, it's more difficult sometimes now I can do text is available in second edition in Sanskrit many, most are not. And English. Well, I do my best. I've been learning English from readings since I was young. And I read a lot of poetry drama, novels and essays.
So it's the English English literature. I do not necessarily mean the English of dictionaries, because I don't we have to use the dictionaries, and lexicographers have done wonderful things for us. made wonderful tools for us. But we have to always be cautious and also look outside the toolbox. And sometimes fine now use words that are not dictionaries. So this is a big topic actually, they're trying to find this layered. Understand this layered nature or what we are doing. We have what in translation theory may be called target language language, we are translating into source language language we're translating from, it's actually more complex than that. So this is a big thing people need to think about think originally. Consider reflect. Meditate, experience. This is a phantom sister just pulled it off the web. I don't even know what it is. Next, please. So maybe the sky is a palimpsest to with the original text is the empty sky. Clouds are the new writing on the sky experience. Experience Experience. So how did I translate? I'm going a little bit backwards and expresses anything there. Yeah. So this is an example of my method in the early days. I use notebooks that we could get in here in Bangkok. And I would generally call those doesn't show perhaps so clearly. Use some The left hand page for the draft translation, the right hand page for notes. So this may be very strange to people who have grown up in a digital age. But I found that very useful. These are, these were done 40 years ago, somehow I still have a big pile of them. Now to come to the book it's divided into four main parts. And the introduction, long introduction has these seven parts. I would like here just go into 12345. Now there's a section. Next, please. Maybe it's coming. Well, let's go through the order of the slide. You can see here is one of the four great living cannons as I mentioned before, I respect them all equally as found fountains funds of the Buddha's work is foundational fundamental for the practice of the Dharma. They're all invaluable. So don't put exactly a hierarchy there. Next place my approach to translation I do not follow any conventional translation theories. I enjoyed reading Kench. And I want to make texts available to others. That was perhaps my initial motivation and translation helps us helps me understand the text. So I wanted the translations to be useful and beneficial. That is for who Gemma hedaya Oh, Jenna sokaiya. And so on. So the purpose of translating is to elephant, people who read the texts. Now I have one example here, which I discuss. Maybe in the forthcoming book, tough times. But that's dasa in the Ponyo was a great teacher in Thailand. And I was privileged to have
his we met him that's four times. Now a phrase that took me praise you use that took me impressed me from the beginning was some tongue lie myconian man to the man. This is his translation from Poly Sunday the man Albini way sigh. Yeah. Now when you read the Valley, it's very effective. Very simple. I think it goes directly to the heart. How to translate maybe nothing whatsoever is worth clinging to. Nothing whatsoever is worth clinging to same God that was originally no thing. So one is nothing next no thing settled difference in English, don't be attached to anything. Don't cling to anything. Now, they have a long section on this going book. One of our main problems is clinging it's fair to say that clinging grasping and attachment lie at the crux of the human problem. Clinging is humanity's hang up. So the Buddha's advice advice is clear. Let it go Let it be dropping. As he says in this short and succinct sub the manner in a way Cya in Paoli, the short phrase is transparent and to the point, there are only four words that I find myself I find it hard or impossible to express indirect and natural English, but those are some possibilities there. Now when we look, when we translate difficult things, even easy things, things easy. The phrase provides good example of the vagaries on might say caprices of the translation over a periods of nearly a century we've come to become a body. This is simple and straightforward. Nothing is worth adhering to. Nothing is worth holding to the earlier ones next place. Nope, sorry. Maybe they are the ones who are not there. Oh, yeah, I haven't sourced them that's in the paper, the book, there should never be an inclination towards any mental states whatsoever. It is not fitting that there shouldn't be inclination should any psychophysical conditions are things ought not to be adhered to. It be fits not to be engrossed in the things of this world. Now you have to think about these two, get the point. And I think they all lack punch. All of them are, right, more or less. But whether they are appropriate or effective is another question. So this is an example of a complication complications we meet in Pali translation. And this also applies to all all types of translation. Next, please. So what is translation? Now these are just a few things I pulled off the internet, very irresponsible way to do it with Anthony Burgess. He says, for contemporary people. Translation is not a matter of words only. It is a matter of making intelligible a whole culture. Now, I don't know exactly what his context was. But this fits very much for what we are doing with translations of Kanjur and tenger. It's not just the words, there's a whole culture there. I had a discussion, one simple put Gaia under the 24. Before 1000 project, about just the name of a certain kind of shoe in the Tibetan finia. And learning people, including some Dong Rinpoche explained how it is understood in Tibetan and I could see that existing translation in English was not correct. So
he goes into the culture. The vinyasa is particularly the federal Italo Calvino without translation, I will be limited to the borders of my own country. The translator is my most important ally. He introduces me to the world. So are translations of can German ginger Tibetan cannons introduce introduced these cannons to the world I didn't fully explain the metaphors Title I shouldn't know if I'm running out of time yet.
There you can take as long as you like there's no rush.
Okay, just wake up with matte finish. Terra Incognita is Bhoomi Lumia AR Gafta unknown slant. This also this bottle of linguistic complexity here in Canada and the Gafta or in cognita Gafta are cognate words kick sunt. They own this Santa is actually Santi are. So the nice translation offered to me by motya Salvini is roomier our gap down as after some he has seen these are terms from old maps. They would have a big blank space. Places that were not known in the 16th centuries and say 17th century and they would call it terra incognita. In some cases there will be a picture of a lion. And I'd say pick some his son to be honest. There are lions here. So when I began the Kanjur was a for me unknown land and terra incognita. That's simply because all we had I had was those catalogs Very little was translated apart from fairs masterful work. So, it was an unknown man. But in that van there are lions Santi has seen that means shark kissing Shakyamuni Shaka the Buddha and the lion of the shark, yes. So, this was my kind of inspiration. Now, very briefly the situation has changed or the SE has improved, there have been more translations more books about the Kanjur there is the 84,000 project, which has made enormous project and my progress towards translating the Kanjur into English. So, but is still a large part is unknown. And the lions are still there. They will always be there. Let's not worry about that. We could also say that there are Gaggia naugus. Elephants another name for the Buddha is Ananda ganja. So that is the title, which sort of is meant to encapsulate my idea, okay. That's good. The book is divided into four, four broad sections is are the, as I mentioned in in the introduction to the book and elsewhere, this is not a collection of any particular canon, any particular school, or anything like that is my personal selections over 50 years. And then I divided them into four thematic sections, but that again, is arbitrary and expense. The important section of the introduction I'd like to emphasize here is things like title and so on. Is history. Texts in any language not far from the sky like Bundala, flowers, every text as a history, or histories or clusters of history, complex. And questioning, the Buddha introduced the history of each subject or nine headings. You can see them I feel it's important for our readers to have some historical, social, philosophic, whatever contexts to understand what they're reading. Now, the main thing is the sutra and your understanding, and the translators understanding. However, this background knowledge, which changes when new information comes, I feel it's very important.
And so these are the ones that I did was history, sources and resources. Where do these texts come from? Which manuscripts were they preserved? The title needs to be explained the translators, we need to know how they are, as you know, in Tibetan we know very little about the early translators of really just their names. Sanskrit versions, I mentioned, whether or not these exists, six out of 25 book exists in complete Sanskrit versions. There are some fragments of others or cetaceans. 16 have none, nothing available in Sanskrit. Last time I looked, new manuscripts are being discovered published and this is a fluctuating field. Sanskrit version does not mean the same version that is translated into Tibetan so they can differ. It could be a different manuscript tradition that has survived in Sanskrit and could be the earlier one it could be later one or whatever. So we have to be very cautious and not give priority to the Sanskrit if it differs from the Tibetan without check it great carefully, Chinese translations, there seem to be 10 of the 25 Chinese translations. Now this shows something that I cannot stress maybe adequately is that the Kanjur is a Buddhist canon in its own right. It has usually been used in western scholarship, let's say, modern scholarship as a kind of backup to Sanskrit or Chinese versions, not given its own full authority. So that's, in these translations, I have used the Tibetan as the kanji version as the primary text as the main text, and if the Sanskrit is different, I may mention it or a may not. Because that primary text is a is the text accepted as primary by the translators, and studied in Tibet as the primary text or variants and so on. So the kanji text is the primary text. Now that brings the problem comparison with Chinese which, of course commodity to project? Does they have the use of the access, which I don't have? That's an ignorant person to the wealth of terminology and translation into Chinese. That is another question. In translating into Chinese, of course, this has to be handled very differently. And it's very significant to enrich the translations through the existing weighty Chinese tradition. But in my case, since I do not know Chinese, I do not compare much for that I have to rely on reliable Scott, colleagues, and there are ones who do help me in this. But I think that for my purposes, I want to make a complete and reasonable translation. And if starts, as you probably know, from the very beginning, when we sit down making something Bhagawan and then the number of big shoes or body sutras in the assembly, if there are four or five Chinese translations of Sanskrit version, and Tibetan version, they can all be different. Now, that's an interesting question historically, yes. But I don't know if it's really a great help to the reader of a translation today, who wants to read an integral text to start out the beginning to say oh, by the way, it's 1250 this version, but in the tongue translation is 15,000 and so on. So I do not stress that these are aspects to the historical development of the text which is related to but not entirely, part of translation. citations and references is the suit just cited in Indian I use Indian and Indic portraiture largely in Vedic that means, Indian texts in Sanskrit or other languages or translated into Tibetan or Chinese. That means that I do not go into the number of citations or references that may be found in works by Tibetan scholars. That is a huge project I mentioned a few. And it is important in a way for the that's for the impact of the text in Tibet, or in China. So that is for detailed study, only doing 25 sutras gets a little bit over modern studies and translations. From the text I used here, there are not so many, these are very important. To mention in your work of tomorrow, Jeeva the same. And hopefully, there are I know, some modern translations into Chinese, some of the texts, and there are the translation modern translations of the Chinese versions. And I hope you can pay attention to be modern studies in European languages, now the setting that's in the new Donna Sravasti, etc, Roger grid, and then a brief summary of the contents. So that I give for each of the 25 sutras. In the forthcoming book, I do something similar. I do give this historical perspective and that under these rules, rubrics, next please.
So that's it. There's no next one. This is the last one.
Oh, I think we skipped some, didn't we? Yeah, there's
some in the middle, I think. Oh, those
notebooks again? Yeah. Look at those notebooks. Yeah, if you can find this. Yeah, this was about my technique, I actually, I count them now skill books. I still prefer to work like this. Because you'd have a record of what you have translate what you have done. And with IRS past, it gets messier and messier. So just I pulled out a heap of them. And found most of these never been transcribed. And I didn't finish them. They're sort of workbooks, copy books, Google Books. So I filled that filled these notebooks. So this was then for my own understanding my own development, that I found several interesting sutras in there that I used to work on. So there is no next
I can show more of your notebook, if you want me to pull out more pictures.
No, I'm very ashamed. Oh, there's one. Yeah. Shame, they're so messy. And I can see they're not even not even dated, I can see historically that my handwriting gets worse. That's probably because my desk gets more and more crowded, and I don't have space to write properly. So the old ones are very nice, readable. That is up to of course, you translators. And you know how you choose to make drafts. I think everyone now uses computer, I still scribble a lot. And then the next day, I can't make sense of it, I can't read my own writing. So that brings the subject of the three graphy study script. So these are all very necessary things. This is a very complex topic. As you have seen, I have more scribbles that I
just quickly run through this sort of slogans in a way, one for the background of language, all the language is read, read, read means to read through texts, whether it's on the screen if you like that or in a book, for example, to read the profession of wisdom. Start with the Heart Sutra and then read the Diamond Sutra and read the long sutras just read through and don't worry, my advice is not worry about every little word. A lot of things will come if you read through. So read, read, read that brings and then also read things outside the box for cultural history, language history. There are writers for English like David Crystal who makes very useful small books very learned sense of humor, read good writers, I cannot say anything about China for Chinese for this. But for English, I mean, are the classical writers, early writers Shakespeare on for the cultural background for India, we read archeology to pick graphy art history, and iconography and so on. Why? How do these relate to translation? Well, I think they are the direct traces of Buddhism in India, especially the inscriptions, he picked graphy. So they are very valuable to read. I don't see much go into that. That's polemical, to not follow trends, but to follow your own heart or wisdom, to ask questions to be up to date. That means, I think in particular, nowadays, keep in touch with new manuscripts studies that come diary texts in particular, and also our archaeology, or new discoveries. The old masterpieces manuals are out of date. So we have to try to keep up too much up to date. And finally, I'd like to say that I and think, think think think Rain, rain, rain, think, think, think. And think outside the box, and to think poetically. And so to maintain a strict personal epistemology, that is to ask for the sources we have. For the information we have what is the source of this piece of knowledge, you need to understand the source to evaluate, it's what it means to us or to the context of our work. Now, I have a long section, which is too long, always, that is the acknowledgments for my work, practice. Now, there's really two long ones, book that is a whole page of it. So there is this little litany of names. In this case, I would start like to start with some secondsI repo chair for his encouragement of not only my humble work, but of these translation projects in the very idea of the importance of translation. And his non sectarian open minded attitude to the encouragement of Tavi studies, in addition to investment studies. So thank you, Mr. Chair for encouraging people to think out for himself thinking outside the box and being a supreme example of that. And there are others that can say foundation like Anjali Ji, and everyone there for their wonderful support. And others in Tibetan studies, poly studies and so on this whole marvelous Indras. Net of people this particular occasion. I thank Jennifer and Shanghai, me and everyone else in Taipei for managing to put this together and Jennifer for helping with the PowerPoint because I'm not capable of these things. And so all of that, so I thank you all. I think that's more than enough from me for the moment. Thank you all for listening and I hope all of your translations of your work will proceed smoothly and joyfully
Thank you very much Professor Peter skilling. And so I just saw that in the comment box there's a comment by Mark Taz. So you know when you put up this slide, the sabay dama Nurlan bien de Versailles. He said cons, I think would say settle down in. So he has a comment from what con was the cons with translate, settle down in. Is that?
Thank you. Yeah, well, there's always disagreement about the choice of terms. And I've been the visa is an extremely important term, found here in poly suta, in Majima, nicaya, and from elsewhere in the Pali canon, but very prominent in the structure per meter, which is probably the way ever Canons translated in Project paramita would be this settled down in. And I have a great respect for his translations, which were some of the first ones that were available in some of the first messages that came from the terra incognita back in even the 60s and 70s. So thank you for the comment.
Okay, so I think what we were going to do is to proceed with the q&a, these questions, the there's a sort of a core group at the kumana Jeeva project they are preparing, we'd have four sessions, reading through some of the materials from the from the book, and they prepared some questions and then others. I think the panelists, panelists can just unmute themselves and speak, is that correct? So if they could, they could also perhaps, you know, make comments and also ask questions, don't write. And then otherwise, other participants attend. People attending the talk can also leave the questions in the q&a or in the chat box. And so we'll try to, to look for those questions. So Jennifer, do you want to start with some of the questions from the, from the group who are meeting to discuss the book?
So we have about 11 questions. So Professor, we will try to put other people's question here if there's anything come up from the question q&a section. So the first question from our group is, Can Professor share when you decide to translate particular sutra? Do you have a work process that you can share with us? And is there some other specific things you would like to advise us apart from Read, read, read? And then the space? Is there anything else you want to add in terms of how to work? Thank you?
Thank you. That's a very good question. And as I say, since I am ignorant of the Chinese, I don't know whether the methodology will be the same. It's too complex to enter and hold lecture can be done unless the work process but as I said, I, first I suppose I seek the Indic terminology, I'm very uncomfortable. If I'm translating something from Tibetan, where I don't know the terminology, I get insecure. And some that is a long term process if it's not in it. If it's not in other dictionaries, it means searching reading, translation Sanskrit texts looking for that word. I can go on for days. I have not been able to mention all the tools that are now available. When I began there were not many in the interim located Chandra has produced several versions of a Tibetan and Sanskrit dictionaries. And Maggie, Mr. Nagy at Sarnath has produced a wonderful what is it? 14 volume, Tibetan Sanskrit dictionary. And again epistemology. So when we look for the Sanskrit term, we also have to be cautious, because some dictionaries just give to any old term, they can't without checking its context. One of the great scholars sort of Chandra Das, maybe Tibetan, one of the first that's an English dictionaries, he will give Sanskrit equivalents from his not from his wide knowledge as a Sanskrit Pandita. So he would use things that are not actually historically used, and so on. So we have to check, where does this come from? And Nagy is very good for that he gives the source and he even cites the context. So gives us some context. So I am translating things from most of them from the early period, let's say around the 800, the year 800. And so if I see that a sense of equivalent is from the 11th century work about pramana, or some other subjects, I cannot consider that necessarily related to the earlier sutra. Translation I'm working with. So there's a lot of exploration in that. So the rule of thumb is always to be to cast the net wide, but to be very cautious.
Okay, very good. Some Shall we just insert some of the questions from from the audience. So we have one question coming from Sharp Chen. He says, Thank you, Professor skilling. This is a very beautiful and inspiring talk. Can you please share your thoughts about what do you think about collaboration among translators, especially in the modern digital and information, data, a era
I think collaboration is always a good thing. From the beginning. The Tibetan translations were collaborations between Indian Indian conductors, and Tibetan scholars. And that was one of the great collaboratory projects, translation projects of all time. This creation of the Kanjur was the sort of pre STAR project before UNESCO, or any such things. So it comes from collaboration. And it should continue as collaboration. I have, let's say informal collaboration with the Tibetans and others. And I mentioned some of them in my early period there. And up to now, I am fortunate to have colleagues who put up with my questions and help me in my attempts to work as for the digital and so on, I'm sort of too old for that. I never got into the habit. Right. They seem to be good things. But again, everything has to be done with caution. And I also find can be a bit overwhelming. And I can't quite balanced that for my own personal idea. Yes, absolutely. Collaborations are good. But there has to be some careful guidelines or way to work out how to do it otherwise, if it's open. I see on the internet, when someone puts an open question, they often get a dozen answers or more. And half the answers are not really relevant at all. And they're people don't understand the question, bring something in which actually might be interesting, helpful in another mean, and so on. So I'm not very good at that except, I think to use, we use all our tools with caution.
Okay, so All right. We maybe will move on to the panel. One of the questions that was that came up in a discussion. So can we move to maybe the next one or one of those? Okay. So we have the third. You mentioned, Professor skilling, you mentioned, where's the third? Okay, I have I have a I have this year actually. Yeah. Okay. You mentioned that we should focus on core teachings of the Buddha. You mentioned, the four summaries for seals. Although you mentioned it was excellent that you chose 25 sutras? Are the four summaries in the core teachings do you wish to focus on when you translate? Or are these are there? Are there other causes and conditions that made you choose these sutras? And one thing I find very interesting. In the book in the introduction, Peter skilling, Professor Peter skilling mentioned, the sort of the Common Core of perhaps the in the early train artists use the word early in, in the the different Nick, is there is a common maybe in any class, I'm not sure it was also between the guys in the hyaena, Common Core, you mentioned something about that. To me, it seems I haven't heard other people sort of discussing this. And that would be also maybe related.
Ah, this is a deep question to how I chose them and how they relate to the four seals and so on. As I say, I had the great privilege of having time. And I was not a I'm an academic quest of any sort at that time. So I could just read the dough, mainly the dough section of the Kanjur, for the year two, and have these Tibetan scholars who I could visit and ask questions, and they will make Tibetan tea, which is a strange thing to have maybe in the hot climate of Bangkok. So I read and I think I do say somewhere in the book, I enjoyed certain texts, they appealed to me. And that was why I decided to translate them, they were lively, meaningful in different ways. So I translated them and actually, for my own understanding that time, so I didn't really apply, I would say that time before seals, because I think they are the they do express very much the core of the Buddhist teaching. I am not one to go through texts, interrogate them, whether they are genuine or not, because they belong to fulfill all four. I don't think that's the point. These are the living kind of living spirit of the texts. So insofar as these texts were part of that spirit, I think I don't go for the sectarian criteria Yes, the core teachings are there often implicitly, rather than explicitly Thank you.
Okay, so, Jennifer, do you want to go to the to sort of the next one in the in the list of the questions?
I think in your book, you mentioned that you will consider the Tibetan Canyon Tango belongs to the Indian Buddhist literature. So, in terms of the knowledge we need to have to translate the Tibetan canon, can you share with us how do we enrich our knowledge of that?
Good question, difficult question. In general costs, this is kind of, could be controversial statement. And we use English words like belong implies I can imply inclusion. So, Tibetan culture and tender is the treasure of Tibetan literature. But at the same time, no contradiction at all. It belongs to it's based on Indian Buddhist literature. Therefore, to understand, I say we should try to have a knowledge of Indian history and culture, which are encapsulated, well expressed. So how to get this knowledge is difficult, read, read, read. And I have said that the old again, in Chinese you have a whole different
library
to read these things. So, if I'm talking about modern academic study of Buddhism, and the relation of Indian history and culture to Buddhism, that's a vast field. Not only in China, of course, we aren't Chinese, but in European languages and Japanese, Korean modern scholarship, great quality. So I don't know how much time you want to invest in this. But it's good to have a background as I say, translating some of the technical terms like a type of Sandor type of tree or bush and the similes you have we have to try to get in the background and the main starting thing for these is to know the Sanskrit term power palimpsest term and then to seek that out to them you can be driven to despair, because our classical classic Sanskrit dictionary, Monier Williams, he will give as do the Indian lexicographer is a single word as multiple meanings. So give up to 510 more, and almost in every one there will be something like a flower type of flower sometimes with a scientific name. And then you check another dictionary and it's a different flower. So things are very difficult to resolve sometimes. I won't talk about here it's complicated. There are some things are untranslatable. That means there's different meanings to translate ability, but some things are maybe not too complicated for a our translation purposes. To translate. Therefore, we use the Sanskrit I would use the Sanskrit term, if I'm not sure about the Tibetan term and put that in a footnote. But trans and translate ability is something we need to recognize and of course, is controversial. Like dharma. Do we translate Dharma is dharma translatable, and there is dharma as dharma as teaching. So Dharma, good Dharma, progressive Dharma, whatever. And problem of choosing for multivariant terms, problems choosing one out of 10 meanings, means the ordinary reader doesn't see the depth of the term. And so what does Dharma mean to them? Course dharma as an Sababa, as a Baba, as an entity, and so on. It's different from dharma as a teaching. So this is always difficult. And I think it's worth Why are to be open to discuss. I probably don't say it enough. burden with too many notes, but often one is not sure. And one has to be able to make learn guesses. We've there we can't go too far into footnotes. So in general to know Indian history and culture in in French and English, we have Lamotte idiom lots history of Indian Buddhism. Huge volume, which remains A classic. Many things are out of date. Yeah, that's not his fault. Time does that. So we have to, I think it's best to find a reliable, classic that brings all this together, and then be aware of new developments. So in archaeology, there are discoveries like Canada, HMI stupa in South India, with a new body of Prakrit inscriptions related to Buddhism. That's not that's unknown to my mom, and two other early writers. So we have to, again, epistemology, we have to find out what are the good sources for these new discoveries. And there is no summary for that. Gun diary manuscripts have changed the whole map of Buddhist studies, I would say.
We do have Richard Solomon's early and later books, the latest one from wisdom publications. But even then, that is very reliable and reasonable. But there are new discoveries. So I suppose Richard will have to write another summary can vary studies in another five years, whatever. So everything changes, I have to try to keep up with the latest reliable information. So it's difficult we used to think, be able to think this past was safe. Yeah, the teeth come from it. The past was safe, it was past. But the past changes, because when we study the past, we study now. But Indian archaeology, Indian history is changing all the time. And that is a problem. To keep up with. Thanks, please.
Let me bring one from the q&a. So this is a sort of long, it starts by saying, Professor, do you ever revise your own translation from many years ago? How important is it for for translators translation style to be consistent and when one's individual style may naturally evolve over time? And then I'll I won't read the whole thing, but it reads also one interesting question. So it says that in the Chinese Buddhist canon used quite often, there are many translations of one same text. Whereas in the Tibetan translation, typically only one translation are always true, typically, only one translation, and then it's revised by others. So revision versus multiple translations that so that situation in relation to what a translator modern day translated might do in terms of revision or whatever.
Thank you, this is a very good and insightful question. These translations that I made in these notebooks, 30, or 40 years ago, or more, have been constantly revised. When I found some new Sanskrit passage or something, I would go to the notebook and scribble it into the middle of the rest of the scribble. And then they were put on the computer. And they were revised. And then I prepared them with the idea of publishing them. So they all revise all of them as I went through, and then at a certain point, I submit the manuscript to the publishers. And from that point, I try not to revise and I keep it at that. This is difficult for me, I'm a compulsive reviser. And sometimes it takes days, weeks, months years for the right words are just popped out. And then I want to change it and yeah, I would. However, I think there's an advantage in print I'm favor, very much print books like this. And there is an advantage that there's a stable translation to go with. When we use when we publish in digitally, we can change it anytime. Yes, but we can't keep track exactly of what we did before. So, yeah, that's too cheap to keep both the original and updated translations. From my own, I think I wouldn't bother or need to the Chinese can just Chinese cannons at a different principle than the Tibetan of keeping the different translators work. So that's a great treasure for following the text. They are chronically. And we have to be careful here too, with our attitude, that we shouldn't think it's the same text translated differently. They are using manuscripts, we often don't really know the origin. But the manuscripts are from different periods. And were made in different places. There were changes in language, the shift from Buddhist practice leads into heavily Sanskrit taper, sensitized languages. So these are part of the natural development of the text. And yes, there is a development but it's not actually linear. Checks was being changed in Nalanda. But another version was there in the lobby could be changed another version of Kashmir. So it's complex and working very valuable to study these developments, but not with a rigid, many year. interpretation. So yeah, having different translations provides a well rounded perspective. Yes, but the original source texts can be a difficult concept, because we don't know what the original is. I should add here very briefly, this is another session. Subject deserves the whole lecture. related only to the argument, portraiture. I think it's key concept of vessel bundle, that the base case is in Sanskrit, is preserved in Sanskrit and mentioned in several of his works, is moola, gitI. Bronk Shaha, that the route, the original, some gitI, the original collection, chanted after the brothers pray, Nirvana is broken up, doesn't exists, damage destroyed, Wallace and gitI puncture, silver, so banjo in was fourth century. That was a principle of his interpretations that there was no surviving for text, as we say, in English, German.
And that applies. We look at the Mahayana, which is outside the Strava consume meaty, same thing with quest for this Waller is problematic, worth doing. Now, the Kanjur they seem to have the policy of one translation. And we find that there are some duplicates here and there. And particularly, the one translation only seems connected, especially with the telfa side of graphs. And many of the local collections, many local congers have become available, scattered throughout the Himalayas, they often preserve different translations, and therefore, we should look at those two.
And so, Tibetan is, I think, very robust and a valid exchange of ideas about translation. And we can see maybe disagreements by some as to how things should be translated. Now is this it's difficult to say I think the ones I translated here didn't have many strong variants. One of them does. That's the Dharma sutra is diff within the Sanskrit from Divya Vedanta. are different in the Tibetan translation. Chinese translation or translations are also different in the number of sanction benefits of dharma, and the phrasing to it's very complicated. So it's necessary to look at these things. And to understand that we have two options, you have different options. And one is to, which I have done here is choose the single text, the Kanjur as the root text, and a root in its own right.
Okay, Jennifer, you have the next one on the screen already.
Yes. I want to share that progressive with people who have participated in a reading session, we were all praising how beautiful your English is. And just wondering how do you have any suggestions on how to develop our mother tongue writing ability? And also do can you share with us what kind of books you normally enjoy reading?
In relation to that there's one in Chinese in the q&a box. He said, that says could Professor recommend his own sort of list of books that he reads? But I mean, that's too long, but we can spend the whole session two sessions just hearing what it's, but I think it's someone related to that question. So I guess I put it there as well.
Well, thank you for saying that my English writing is beautiful. It's painful going through talking about revision revision goes on all the time. And I, part of my technique is for the translation and even for commentary is once I am more or less finished, to read it out loud, especially the translations, because translation, language is communication is oral. And the beauty is in the often in the sound of the words, not only what we see on the page. So how I got this, I don't know I mentioned earlier, that I was fortunate to read a lot in my youth, to read a lot of poetry, literature on My own initiative, but at the same time, the Canadian school system, when I was young was still fairly academic. We will read Shakespeare's plays, we will read sonnets. We've learned Latin, I was the last generation, I mean, dinosaur, last generation in Ontario, different systems, you know, in the province of Ontario, in the last generation, that had to learn much compulsorily. And that was a great benefit, I can see I can use the Latin much anymore. I can recognize the words in the title, for example of this talk. But because Latin has a family relationship with Sanskrit, and we've learned French because Canada was a bilingual country, I think it's now multilingual, even better. But anyway, that is very important when you are young to be exposed to different languages. So I have marched we English, it's a French Introduction to Literature and enjoyed that, at that time. Reading Buddhist texts was, well when I was 10, or 11. There were a few things to read. But not many. There were books on Zen. Cha cons. Kanzi was one of the first people to do extensive translation work and make anthologies which are still useful. So the favorite books are what I read now is a little complicated and antiquated. notes here I read a lot of thought Reading I still read a lot of poetry and they have this full Oxford collection of selected cartas Sutras of Shelley. Now I wondered about this book recently. It's a beautiful book, mask of hammer key. And so I was very fond of Shelley. And in fact, I took this book with me, from England through Europe. That's 19 I guess, and then carried it to India, because it was in my bag. And by chance I went to India, that's another story. And it's still here. So there are moving the poet's is important. There are books by Kumara, Swamy, Buddha and the gospel of Buddhism. I don't know if you can see them.
These are reprinted probably online. He has a beautiful writer. And we should not look down on books because of their
language appears antiquated. So I'm like I would never use or rarely use the word gospel. To understand why. So in the early translations used a lot of Christianized vocabulary, because English language is deeply saturated by the language of the Bible King James Bible prediction. And so it's standard. So hi, many expressions have gone enjoy. But I don't read that very much. Favorite Books is difficult, I'm I have less time than I would like to read the books I get, I tend to correct. Try to read translations playtest, disagree, discoveries on archaeology, art, and so on. So it's a bit hard to say. And I'm always pulling up old books too. But it's a wide range from including anthropology, world history, and so on. But I do have in my scribbles here to about to be being cautious about the latest fashions. There is a tendency in which I think computer helps, because don't keep hold things are only the new things to follow the latest fashion or terminology. And that immediately can date. Yes, it can take my translation, if I use a term term used by Shelley Hill, in St. James Bible, or used by TS Eliot or whomever that that is a choice, particular word for its sound and meaning. Just to choose the latest slogan, these words often vanish within a year or two. So I do recommend not following the latest trend, just because it's the latest, that's the problem there things are this is trending so many people think oh, I have to follow that. I have to say that I have to discuss that. I think that no, we're not balanced in this draft. But the translation choice of the term is doesn't come from the dictionary doesn't come from the latest literature. It comes from the heart from the store of knowledge. So each translator each writer has to build up their own dictionary each word something have your property for me for example, with Sanskrit terminology that is a pig or a word is the now you take the Sanskrit translation and on that pig, I start to hang things. Things hey are attracted like mag magnets around that. Various terms. Concepts are key So favorite books I can say right now?
Okay, so the next one, most of the students develop translator translator training programs. So this is the managing translation project has its own translator training program that they have not studied studying Sanskrit they had to study Chinese literature, Tibetan, both oral and written and dharma in our program in the first two years. Can you give some advice on the study of Sanskrit, if they wish to trust a kangaroo and thank you in the near future?
Well, I mentioned this briefly earlier. Okay. Is a problem related to the palimpsest principle? Yes, you have to study Chinese literature about which I know little except in translation with that is the source for understanding the terminology, the vocabulary, and the style and the standards that you will use. So I can't really can't comment on that I study Chinese Literature Through translations and I study trends with changing translations like the Tao Te Ching or tonsor, excuse my pronunciations, I have a dozen translations of each and if a new one comes and that's the same principle is there that I mentioned Indian Studies, new manuscripts have appeared being edited, translated discussed and so on, for these classics like The Book of the bow allowed to discuss that in question, but in the introduction, there are many scripts earlier than anything we have in India. Now, for the study of Sanskrit is not easy, as I said for the poem problems stick sexism aspect of translation to build up a reliable vocabulary of equivalents, Sanskrit equivalents of Tibetan terms and their China and Chinese translations, which of course, was mentioned there sometime four or five translations of the same sutra, more and these translators choose different terms. So even the translation history of a single term is complex. But so, apart from the grammar, part from the reading ability, building up a vocabulary of Sanskrit equivalents is important and useful. And you can use Sanskrit dictionaries, or other such works. reading texts after getting some noise or sensory reading texts that are not too complex grammatically, like the perfection of wisdom, Chechen texts, really matter side by side with the Tibetan is very helpful. Learning Online, I'm not too knowledgeable about this, there are programs now by organized by Matteo Salvini at the International Buddhist College in Thailand, Malaysia, I think is checking out what kind of courses he prefers. Of course, this is going to take time and take energy, but that is very helpful. And venerable diamond Jyoti in Hong Kong also has produced some books of studying Buddha's Sanskrit, because this is a difficult question in a way too. If you have standard Sanskrit courses or coursebooks. They are mainly the examples that you have to read are mainstream Hindu Romanenko classical Indian works, which is fine, that's wonderful to be able to read those But if you're focusing on Buddhist texts, it may not help so much. So learning to read sutra, Sanskrit versus Sanskrit sutra language, is, is very, is a better way to go, I think. And that's why I also refer to reading the perfection of wisdom or some prose sutras because once we go into verse,
it's more difficult and to be able to read Abbe Dhamma, Kosha, the characters, the verses of the, I mean, I'm cautious, a wonderful thing, but then it's not easy. And so, that will come if you keep it up. So I would suggest looking for what is related online program, programs Matea has sent the web address for that. And that is one way to go into think more. I think we have to think seriously about that. Find a way that does not set the standard too high. To expect read great poems like moto cheetah is beautiful poetry. Early praises of the Buddha, which for me are very hard. So start with something simple vocabulary, build up. Things you can read, and then carry on.
Matthew, Professor Matthew Savini is now in the pet is one of the panelists. Would you like to just speak about the programs that you have? If you could sort of unmute yourself and
presently, is he in the audience or in the panelists?
No, I think he was made a panelist. But I don't know if it's exceeded in not yet. But I thought I saw some
maybe can you Professor, can you raise your hand we will add you?
Oh, okay. Thank you. Yes, now, I was able to unmute myself. Thank you very much. Thank you very much Professor skilling for mentioning our programs. Well, yes, we have several courses, which focus on Sanskrit in our college, and we welcome auditors as well. And also, I provide some didactic materials in our YouTube channel called saga dam, which is connected to Facebook accounts and we are going to have a website as well and there where there is some material also for complete beginners. That can gain some basic familiarity with Sanskrit by chanting some simple Buddhist texts. Besides that, I have written grammar of Sanskrit, which is still a work in progress, but it has been used, especially by the Mongolian center. And so there are ongoing courses they're using my grandma, also at Dharma realm, Buddhist university. Both of these are located in California. So I would recommend those having a look at those courses, which are taught by very good Sanskrit tastes. And we've focus on the Buddhist elements of Sanskrit learnings. However, anyone is welcome to contact me as well. If they want to have further information. I will also leave my email on the chat and I can offer more precise information to whomsoever might be interested.
Okay, thank you very much, Professor Savini. Think we could just move on to let me see that was number seven.
professedly This one
says can use share looking for? It's a short one can you share how you collect or access so much recently? paper's Sanskrit texts from Thailand, do you have a big collection of books at home? Out of curiosity? Are these special? Are there special Sanskrit database that you normally use?
I can't say anything about the database. I think Professor salva need to tell you more about that. I started studying here, let's say about 50 years ago. Now in those days, I would go every a certain point, I would go every year or so to Canada, or to Europe, I would go to libraries, list journals, I want them to look up and make photocopies and lug those photocopies back with the still have them. So yeah, I started with photocopies collecting photocopies as for books, basically, the libraries here do not have the research materials that I needed. So I had to buy them collect them. And I did. So I have far too many books that I can read. And I can hardly move around. Because there are so many. They, as you know, I prefer as I mentioned, I generally prefer the book. And I get big piles of books around me on the desk, until I can write properly. So it is important to form your own attitude towards this, some people I know are extremely quick. Pulling up digital files may take me an hour and never find it. So yeah, so you should protect and have a good system of classification for digital files, and use whatever databases are available. And there is a lot of them. I think if you don't mind having books, you have to worry about space, always problem. So that's up to the individual to decide. And libraries. I hope that normal use of libraries, pre pandemic, use of libraries will translate into the same systems for the post pandemic libraries, that is to say researched libraries that keep the latest publications, journals, et cetera, available for reading in the library environment, then you don't have to collect so many books, as I had to do here, for example. So that that means that lectures, students, others should form a good relation with the librarians, with the university staff to keep the purchase of books ongoing. And I think as I say, I believe in books for the long term study. Thank you. So
that pandemic is having an impact on the ability to travel to these research libraries. That's really true for those of us living in Asia, not near a good research library. Okay, so we have this new one, he sent me what you mentioned, our knowledge is incomplete in terms of how Buddhist texts migrated across the Himalayas and settled in a very different language family can you shed some light on and what kind of research topics are really necessary for translation projects like the Kumara Jeeva project 84,000 are independent translators of the Tangier in danger.
Difficult our knowledge is incomplete about many aspects of Indian Buddhism and including its transfer to the land of snows. In fact, there is very little surviving Sanskrit or other material than even mentioned No travel of wood sticks to India. Now we turn into libraries, the great libraries were destroyed. We don't even know what happened to them, as purism declined, disappeared. So there may have been material like this, but we don't have access to it. Tara nada, of course mentions at the end of his job that he mentioned, several of his sources, quite clearly refers to their authors and titles. And now I forget exactly, but one of them, he says, For up to the Father period, I use this. And then a case for the spread of Buddhism to the southern seas, I used this. So there were these kind of historical source books were traveling to Tibet. But unfortunately, no one has come up with any of them, I guess they were destroyed in later periods of the modern period. That's really those would be treasures to find. So the materials are very little. Research really means as is going on, is looking at the manuscript collections in Bhutan, and the HEMA areas where access is possible. And seeing what is there as far as I know, not so much has come. But I think a new conceptual conceptualization of how the texts were transmitted to the Tibetan cultural realm. The Tibetan terror is, in fact needed as a result of, especially I think, University of Vienna has very deciduous study of twin captures in various so called local Kansas, throughout the whole family, it's this shows that the canonical texts and other texts were, well, no, they did disseminate throughout the whole Tibetan area, a Marion area. And so it was not a not an elite wasn't me projects in the way but not an elite project centered in Lhasa, or in the political centers of Tibet, it spread in some of the old manuscripts, like the baton manuscript from you history to that is a very curious one, I think 24 volumes or something survived in the New York Museum. And there there are translations of some texts that were otherwise unknown or lost or different alternate translations in this is a local conjecture might say that it's looks a bit disheveled or bits as to other ones. So finding out about this in terms of actual transmission is very important. So that takes field work dedicated field work and of course, as I said before keeping aware keeping up to date with reliable sources of information for these things
okay
let me see there's one is that already one o'clock? Someone said Well, yes, it is one o'clock so I guess we just have to stop is supposed
to finish at one o'clock. I don't know if you're too tired to continue answering questions or?
Yeah, I can. Do you mean a certain point? It will just go blank or
sorry, when you want wish to stop? You'd let us know.
Okay. Maybe we'll just go for you know, I mean, perhaps an additional 15 minutes also show on to him to be too exhausted by questions.
Okay. So maybe I asked this one. It's basically about how professor can find the site. notation is quite difficult. Even if we use TBRC or bdrc to search, sometimes there's a slight change in the Tibetan, then you can find the citation. So are there specifically ways that you find these citations? Or it's coming from your extensive reading in the past?
Huh? Question, I suppose it's the last their last one there. Citations means you're reading shastra, basically. And then in the shastra, recognizing the text, so what I put from my book here, I think it's fairly accurate for available texts now. And my purpose was probably to look original Sanskrit term citations, or also sometimes to see how a sutra was received by the shastra, writers and so on. So I searched this mainly, it was from just reading, recognizing sutra and writing, cross referencing the margin of the book. Nowadays, there are many. And there are digital versions of both Sanskrit and Tibetan of most of these. But as it says, Here, as you have said, the questioner, the citations might have some slight difference to the original text. Yeah, it makes it difficult to find that is an important point of means shows one of the reasons to try to find them, because you will see alternate translations, alternate translation choices.
But how you can find them? I think it means extensive reading, of course, searching for it. But if you don't find it, extensive reading, and there are sometimes things that are really very important, like the few citations in the commentary to the color Chuck plump, I put the rica he actually quotes Polly, several times. But I don't know if you could find them by searching, either in a sense, or not certainly in Tibetan, but he does call it Magadi which is very interesting. So yeah, receiving, receiving receiving reads and cast your net wide. Fortunately, some of the additions the classic conditions of the Sanskrit texts, by people like Lamott give an index of a list of citations that they have identified at the end. So that's why it is very important, I think for these texts to go back to the original traditions, but great scholars means 890 9/19, early 20th century, now the editions produced in India. Yeah, in the 50s and 60s, gave some of this information to but in less detail. So it's good to get access to the to check the original editions, because later reprints or re editions are often just the original edition plus mistakes, typos and so on. So that's another aspect of our epistemology or studies is the print print editions we use we have to choose carefully. In one of the texts I study the babyzen grantees job, I mentioned in the introduction, historical introduction to that, and when I studied it, I used condition by Shastri. And I think his first versions of that were maybe in the 1950s or earlier no earlier. He used the Tibetan he reconstructed the Viva subgrantee sutra from the quotations in Indian Shastras and published Tibetan, his his translation, and all of this. So that was what I used compared to the otally. The print for the Tibetan at the time, that was what was available. And I recognize the time it's already recognized that is reconstruction might be 40 in some places. But now, in addition of this from an original Sanskrit manuscript in the Potala has been published with her set of 20 Sanskrit texts, as the sutras by actually Vinita sang from Taiwan. So now, the root text study for the Sanskrit is we, her addition of the Sanskrit from a Sanskrit manuscripts, we can still look at and learn from is Swami Shastras. edition. I still respect it for it. It's very useful to me. But now we have to recognize this change. As I say, critical awareness of times of the epistemology of what we're doing is very important. But I can't really help this problem of searching in Tibetan where the translation maybe rent, even a translation of the title sometimes can be different. So the only way to find things just read read read.
Okay, thank you. I think the why don't we just wrap up today's questions with this very last one, I guess it might be appropriate, and to the, to the part of the this part of the talk. So here it goes. Translation is a very difficult and lonely task. Second concern, which is said it is not a sexy job. How do you keep your passion for translation alive in all these years? Or how and what kind of enjoyment do we find in translation?
Now well, I agree with Jay, it's not a sexy job. Especially nowadays, in some places in the west, to no an extra language is considered a burden, and even just even to start, it's not attractive. So keep my passion alive. I suppose I have enjoyed reading the texts. I enjoy reading the texts. Reading them in the Sanskrit reading them in the Tibetan is inspiring. Professor Salvini mentioned using recitation chanting as a tool for teaching Sanskrit and I completely agree with that. And reading out loud, reciting is inspiring. It gives energy here in Thailand, I maybe I'm not a teacher, I don't have the ability. I have been surprised. I used to say that if you know put down Serralunga Charmi. If you know some of the common chants, Namo Tassa and so on, you have the whole grammar there someone can say Ah well, NAMA was this Tessa is that Dagoba tau is that form Bhagawan ATP, so Bagua is that and so on. So it seems that if someone knows the basic chants, they can be taught, probably very easily aligned to see that that is usually done. But I think for sensitive as a course, as a means of a course. I think that is it's very positive way to develop Sanskrit. So I think Gree reading out loud, just being inspired by the texts leads me to translate. So somehow, the passion is still there.
That's great. That's very beautiful. So I think with that perhaps we should wrap up today's talk. And it's wonderful, really, really wonderful to hear from Professor Peter skilling to, to learn so much from his knowledge and, and of course, anyone who has not been able to do so we certainly recommend getting the book question and the Buddha, a selection of 25 sutras with these wonderful translations, and also, these additional resources, citations and modern scholarship has a wealth of information and very lengthy introduction with a effectively a new history of Buddhist literature. And we will learn can learn so much from it. So thank you so much, Professor Peter skinning. And Jennifer, do you want to say some last words to wrap up today's top?
Thank you for resonably Thank you, Professor for just killing it really, it's a really touching, discussion and learn so much from you. I've been getting messages from our team that how inspired they are by your sharing of experience. And I'm sure all the people who've been here also felt the same way. And so Professor, thank you so much for this opportunity, I hope we can talk to you again soon. And we will try to follow devices in our training. And hopefully we can share Chinese translation with the world as much as we can. And, and also, I want to take this opportunity to thank Professor Lee for leading this discussion. And also joy, who has been doing one of the most difficult job of this gathering is doing a Chinese interpretation for our Chinese audience. So Joy, thank you so much for making this doing it from Harvard. So it's actually the middle of the night for hers. So thank you so much. And thank you for everybody who made your time to come and join us, I hope to see you again in our future events, or in our study groups. Thank you, she should die.
Thank you. Thank you for having me. Thank everyone for listening. And remember, I am just a learner. So don't believe everything I say should examine critically. And thank Shanghai and joy and all the others who have put this together. I think it's something that can continue because I didn't of course, because I'm colossally ignorant, I don't know Chinese. But it is important this cross fertilization and don't like this word, networking, overworked word. He's not nice words. This sort of active human intertextuality or intercommunication. Not just conversations between the different what is Canon's? Ultimately, bringing in the valley somehow, which has 10 tends to live in its special box. Always opening the windows. But um, so this kind of common conversation amongst cannons, and different schools, non sectarian is very important. Thank you for all you've done with the Kumara Jeeva project. Thank you.
Thank you, everybody.